One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Get running, get running
holding our flag high in the sky
Cross this endless sea with me and search for
a global miracle no one
has yet been able to find
With our hearts pounding,
we'll just charge ahead as we please, following
the footprints of those who pursue their dreams
No matter how stormy the night,
if we put our minds together,
we'll get through it
always
Get running, get running
holding our flag high in the sky
Even though there are tears
we don't want anyone to see
Keep chasing, keep chasing
the compass that leads to our dreams
always points straight ahead
We can't stop here
Get running, get running,
head past everyone else
So long as we don't run from it,
we can take hold of tomorrow
Keep chasing, keep chasing
everything we see in the moment,
we should record it all
in the blank slates of our minds
Buster Call
H-Hey, look at that!
I've never seen this before!
Yeah, I've never even heard
anyone talking about it!
Incredible! The Gates of Justice
are completely open!
It's so that the battleships from
Headquarters can get through!
It's for the buster call's bombardment!
I'm sure Old Lady Kokoro said...
that those doors never
open all the way.
This is alarming.
What the hell is a "buster call"-waina?
The Straw Hats picked a fight with the world.
So the Navy's ready to obliterate this entire island with them on it-waina!
Bastards!
Don't die, Bro!
Yeah!
Come back in one piece!
Straw Hat!
I left saving Robin to Franky.
I was careless.
I never expected him to be this powerful.
You seem to be struggling to breathe.
Is it because of that steam?
I don't care, as long as I defeat you.
I see. You're tenacious.
I've got to get there in time!
Don't go anywhere, Nico Robin!
Guards, outside!
Yes, sir!
Sentries of the Gates of Justice...
and marines of the Navy Headquarters escort,
Chief Spandam of Cipher Pol No. 9 is currently...
hauling a nefarious criminal across the bridge from the Tower of Justice.
Fall in and salute!
Yes, sir!
Look at that. We're all ready to set sail.
Nothing stands in my way now.
Oh, yeah, Nico Robin.
I'll let you in on a little secret.
I activated a landmine that's set
at the top of the stairs back there.
If, by any chance, someone
tries to make their way here,
the stairs will go boom, sending them flying!
What do you think? Isn't that exciting?
Well, don't worry about it,
since no one's gonna make
it to those stairs anyway.
But I won't go through... the gate...
Huh?
because they said they'd rescue me.
No one's coming, you dumb broad!
They'll all burn to death
in the raging inferno of a buster call!
It'll even erase the utter humiliation of those pirates torching our sacred flag!
It's just like when that giant marine attacked us on Ohara twenty years ago.
Now, walk!
Walk with your own two feet!
Saul...
You bitch!
Chief! Please hurry!
I know! Shut up! I'm a hero!
You probably thought that I didn't
know anything about it, didn't you?
The misconduct by Jaguar D. Saul,
a former Navy Headquarters vice admiral...
Your mother, Olvia...
What happened on Ohara back then...
I know all about it!
Why do you think that is?
That's because I was told.
The man who commanded the raid on Ohara—the land of devils—
exposed their terrible crimes, and issued a buster call...
was the then-CP9 chief—and my old man—Spandine!
Well, scholars of Ohara!
I have found your crimes worthy of death!
Eliminate him!
Professor!
Ohara...
knows too much.
It's time for a buster call!
Farewell, Ohara.
Now, go, Saul!
Are you sure about this?
Yes.
I don't wanna go! I'll stay with you! Mother!
Mother!
I was happy to hear you call me that.
Thank you!
From now on, for you and me both...
Live, Robin!
They thought that everyone on Ohara had died,
but the government missed one brat who escaped.
How was it?
How many times were you hunted down by adults...
who hoped to get rich by killing some eight-year-old kid?
You couldn't trust anyone who approached you.
You had nowhere to sleep safe and sound. No food.
I don't even wanna imagine how crappy
the last twenty years were for you.
Oh, it was so miserable, it makes you wanna cry?
The person who put a bounty
on your head twenty years ago...
was my old man!
He did it for world peace!
Now, twenty years later, his son hunts down the only survivor...
and brings the battle of Ohara to its end.
Ohara lost!
Robin! Hold your head high, Robin!
Your mom is honorable! Ohara is honorable!
Someday, pass down this
island's history, Robin!
Ohara fought against the world!
I'm still alive!
But you're gonna die, aren't you?! Right?!
Whoa! What?!
C-Cutty Flam! What is he doing here?!
But that's fine. The trap worked! What an idiot!
That moron triggered the landmine!
He came to rescue me!
Yikes. That's no good. I'm glad I planned ahead.
We've gotta hurry. Come on!
I have no words.
Hey, marines! Set sail! I'll jump on!
Y-Yes, sir! Roger!
We're setting sail!
Yes, sir!
I'm so upset, I can't stop crying!
Behold!
Here is the first step of a hero that history will long remem–
Are you okay, Chief?!
What was that?! Who did this?!
There's no one on the bridge!
There must be! They must be
hiding somewhere! Find them!
Where are they?!
Hey! What're you guys doing?!
You're all worthless!
But, Chief, we can't locate the enemy!
Ah! There he is!
On top of the Tower of Justice!
The Tower of Justice?! What can he do from all the way up there?!
– Zing!
– Who the hell is that?!
He's hitting us dead on, at that distance, in this wind?!
♪ I was born... ♪
Who the hell is that?!
♪ on the island of snipers. ♪
Long Nose-kun!
See that?! Our sniper is damn impressive!
♪ Or even your heart... ♪
Damn well serves them right!
Robin-chan! Run!
♪ Lock on!! ♪
Does he really have to sing?
How dare you?!
Chief!
Dammit! What're you guys doing?!
Shoot him already!
We're trying, but our bullets don't
reach that far, much less hit him!
That sniper's got outstanding aim!
Nico Robin is getting away!
Don't let her get away!
Idiots! You can shoot her!
– Yes, sir!
– Shoot her dead enough to keep her alive!
Huh?!
Fire!
What?!
What the hell is he?!
It's you.
I'm solid iron, baby.
That landmine wasn't cool, Spanda!
Eek!
Er, Franky-kun, Franky-kun.
This is Sogeking.
Hm? Oh? How'd you get this transponder snail?
From Nami.
More importantly, you should find a red
cloth bundle on the ground near you.
Red cloth?
Yeah, I see it!
It has two keys in it.
With your keys,
you should have them all now.
All the keys?!
I delivered them to you right on target.
Mission accomplished.
Let's hurry. This isn't good.
No. 1...
No. 3...
No. 4... Doesn't work!
No. 5!
They came off!
Nonsense! Th-They're the real keys?!
Hey, hey. Pull yourself together!
Oh, no. That means...
Ahh! You guys defeated all
the CP9 agents in the Tower of Justice?!
No, that can't be true!
You must've stolen them and ran! Dammit!
This is Franky! Hey, Long Nose!
I uncuffed Nico Robin.
Nice!
Thank you, Long Nose-kun!
Thank those who fought bravely
to get the keys when this is all over.
You are, without a doubt,
one of Luffy-kun's crew!
You can now do as you wish!
Yes.
Seis Fleur!
What?! What's going on?!
Slap!
Whoa.
I'll do this to my heart's content.
Chief!
Okay, guys! Hurry and get over here!
I'll get things ready for our escape!
Roger!
Come down already, Sogeking!
This is bad! The criminal is free of the seastone handcuffs!
Capture her again!
Everything went according to my plan.
Hm? What's that?
Did I hear something just now?
What?
What the heck?
It can't be!
Was that cannon fire from a battleship?!
The stockade!
"Justice"
Vice Admiral, that last shot struck the main island's stockade nearest to our four o'clock!
– And?
– Huh?
I'm asking, what's your point?
Yes, sir. Well, nothing really, sir!
This is an indiscriminate attack.
I could care less where we hit.
Yes, sir.
Our mission is to burn it all down.
They decimated the fence that surrounds the island.
That was a huge explosion.
If a bunch of battleships comes and
rains down cannon fire like that...
Also, look.
Those violently surging whirlpools that kept ships away are now gone.
It's because the Gates of Justice were
opened all the way to allow the attack.
Tower of Justice
Sea Currents
Those enormous gates blocked the sea currents, causing those whirlpools.
Now that the gates are open
and nothing is blocking them,
the sea currents returned to normal,
and the whirlpools disappeared, huh?
Which means, the battleships...
will have no trouble approaching the island.
– Sogeking!
– There's no time to lose!
Jump down from there!
How reckless!
First off, it's not like I have
superhuman strength like you guys,
or the courage not to fear death!
I'm just a garden-variety superhero!
Hm?
Usopp!
The Tower of Justice!
Long Nose-kun!
Long Nose!
Look! This time, they hit the Tower of Justice!
The Tower of Justice!
Are they okay?!
As I suspected, the sound
earlier was no ordinary explosion!
That was cannon fire!
Hurry and leave the island!
Wait. He didn't just... right?
Hey! Usopp!
Ahhh!!
You called?!
You're alive!
Hey! Don't you guys have
the decency to catch a hero...
making a desperate jump
off the rooftop?! Morons!
Franky! Robin-chan! We're okay here.
We're heading over right away!
That's a relief.
Well then, let's do something about things here.
Hey, can I count on you to help fight?
Of course.
Hurry up, soldiers! Take care of them before the attack kicks into full gear!
Yes, sir!
There's an escort ship on the
other side of the bridge, huh?
Could that be the key to our escape?
It looks like stealing that ship is our only chance for survival.
Get them!
Razor!
Jet Pistol!
I understand now.
You're basically doping.
You accelerate your circulation
by using your legs as a pump.
The blood pressure gets so high that
a normal person's heart would burst,
but since your organs and blood vessels
are rubber, you can withstand the pressure.
That's a technique only a rubber man could use.
While your physical abilities spike above their usual limits,
you don't have the stamina to keep up the intensity.
That's not really smart.
You know you're shortening your life, right?
It's better than losing everything right before my eyes!
I do whatever I can!
You're too ambitious!
Did you feel the explosion earlier?
That was probably a battleship from
Navy Headquarters running a firing drill.
Before too long, they'll begin their barrage.
Your friends who are in the
Tower of Justice will die there.
Maybe some of them are lucky enough to be running down the tunnel to get here.
Tempest Kick!
What?!
This seawater will flood the passage,
ensuring that anyone in there will drown.
You bastard.
Nothing is going well for you, Straw Hat.
You have this naive idea that you can save everyone and escape.
Let's see how far it gets you.
What're you doing, you jerk?!
Kokoro-san! Chimney! Gonbe!
Thanks for the directions!
Pirate Lady!
I felt quite a shock just a moment ago.
Looks like it's finally gonna start, huh?!
Cannon fire! Cannon fire!
Hurry up!
All you have to do is capture Nico Robin
and put her on the escort ship!
Move it! The battleships are coming!
It looks like we're too late.
What'd you say?!
Ah!
Ahh!
Through the fog,
we can see the ships' outlines!
H-Hey, don't run away! Wait!
Oh, no.
This serves you right!
They're here! They're finally here!
A fleet of battleships!
The buster call has begun!